A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Educational Interests, Series G FA316
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Colleges
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute, 1951-1953 (Box 111, Folder 807)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute, 1954-1955 (Box 111, Folder 808)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute, 1956-1959 (Box 111, Folder 809)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute, 1959-1961 (Box 111, Folder 810)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - James A. Breasted, 1935-1936 (Box 111, Folder 811)
    Breasted's request for permanent endowment; John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s refusal. Breasted's death; closing out his plans; memorial service for Breasted.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - General Pledges, 1919-1923 (Box 112, Folder 812)
    Breasted's first pledge.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - General Pledges, 1920 (Box 112, Folder 813)
    For general work.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - General Pledges - December 29, 1923 Pledge (Box 112, Folder 814)
    Extending 1919 three year pledge.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - General Pledges - June 1, 1927 Pledge (Box 112, Folder 815)
    Covering salaries and expenses.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - General Pledges - April 3, 1929 (Box 112, Folder 816)
    For buildings and land. Pledge cancelled September 1929.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - Project Pledges - December 4, 1928 Pledge (Box 112, Folder 817)
    Assyria Work.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - Project Pledges - October 1925 through April 1926 (Box 112, Folder 818)
    Egyptian Research.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - Project Pledges, 1924-1955 (Box 112, Folder 819)
    July 20, 1929 pledge. Rev. January 31, 1930. Publication of Egyptian paintings.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - Project Pledges - Egyptian Dictionary, 1924-1930 (Box 112, Folder 820)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - Project Pledges - April 19, 1921 Pledge (Box 112, Folder 821)
    Ford Collection purchase.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - Project Pledges - December 5, 1919 Pledge (Box 112, Folder 822)
    Purchase of pieces from Holy Land.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - Project Pledges, 1928-1930 (Box 112, Folder 823)
    Re: proposed contract with Iraq.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - Project Pledges, April 1924, 1921-1930 (Box 112, Folder 824)
    The Excavation at Megiddo.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - Project Pledges - May 2, 1929 Pledge (Box 112, Folder 825)
    Upper Tigris Antiquities.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Investigation Fund - Dr. Ernest D. Burton FC #12 - Correspondence, 1903-1912 (Box 112, Folder 826)
    Excellent Frederick T. Gates letter, 1907, on future of work in China; education how and why. Frederick T. Gates urges Burton be sent to investigate China conditions. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. underwrote part of Burton's trip to Orient. Excellent personal letters describing conditions in Far East. Good policy letters by Frederick T. Gates. Correspondents include Frederick T. Gates, Starr J. Murphy, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Ernest D. Burton, E. Judson.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Investigation Fund - Dr. Ernest D. Burton FC #12 - Correspondence, 1903-1912 (Box 112, Folder 827)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Investigation Fund - Dr. Ernest D. Burton FC #12 - Correspondence, 1903-1912 (Box 112, Folder 828)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Investigation Fund - Dr. Ernest D. Burton FC #12 - Notes on Trip, 1908-1910 (Box 113, Folder 829)
    Daily journal kept by Burton on year's trip through Far East; includes photographs. Correspondents include Ernest D. Burton.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Investigation Fund - Dr. Ernest D. Burton FC #12 - Notes on Trip, 1908-1910 (Box 113, Folder 830)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Investigation Fund - Dr. Ernest D. Burton FC #12 - Notes on Trip, 1908-1910 (Box 113, Folder 831)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Investigation Fund - Dr. Ernest D. Burton FC #12 - Notes on Trip, 1908-1910 (Box 113, Folder 832)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Dr. Ernest D. Burton - Report of Oriental Educational Commission, 1909 (Box 113, Folder 833)
    Final Report on Far Eastern trip. Submitted by Dr. Ernest D. Burton, of the Oriental Institute, to University of Chicago. Correspondents include Dr. Ernest D. Burton.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Dr. Ernest D. Burton - Report of Oriental Educational Commission, 1909 (Box 113, Folder 834)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Dr. Ernest D. Burton - Report of Oriental Educational Commission, December 1910 (Box 113, Folder 835)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Dr. Ernest D. Burton - Report of Oriental Educational Commission, 1910 (Box 114, Folder 836)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - Mt. Sinai Library - February 26, 1930 Pledge, 1929-1931 (Box 114, Folder 837)
    H. E. Fosdick visits library; fears for physical welfare and urges action by John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Rockefeller experts and monks disagree on plans; no Rockefeller aid put into library. Correspondents include H. E. Fosdick, Raymond B. Fosdick, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - Abydos
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributed to cost of hand painted reproductions of painted reliefs of Abydos temple. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. interest in progress of work; publication of work, and John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s pleasure with it. Political problems. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s concern for Miss Calverley's health; Miss Calverley's death. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., James Breasted, A. M. Calverley, Alan Gardner, John A. Wilson.
    - 1929-1949 (Box 114, Folder 838)
    - 1936-1960 (Box 114, Folder 839)
    - 1949-1953 (Box 114, Folder 840)
    - 1954-1956 (Box 114, Folder 841)
    - 1956 (Box 114, Folder 842)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - Abydos - Miss Calverley's Film Project, 1948-1950 (Box 114, Folder 843)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. declined to finance educational motion picture.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - Abydos - June 1946 Pledge, 1946-1950 (Box 114, Folder 844)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contribution toward completion of work.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - "Ancient Egyptian Paintings" - Sakkarah Expedition Abydos Project, 1939 (Box 114A, Folder 845)
    Summary of gifts and expenditures as of April 25, 1939.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - "Davies-Gardiner Paintings" - Sakkarah Expedition Abydos Project, 1936 (Box 114A, Folder 846)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Centenary Exhibition, December 1974 (Box 114A, Folder 847)
    Booklet.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - Abydos - Accounting of Funds After A. Calverley's Death, 1959-1960 (Box 115, Folder 848)
    Closing out Miss Calverley's work after her death. Financial details because of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contributions to her work. Final settlement between Miss Calverley's estate and Oriental Institute. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Hugh Calverley, Dana S. Creel.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - David Rockefeller
    Requests for aid; David Rockefeller's election to Board of Trustees; David Rockefeller comments on Communism at University. Thomas M. Debevoise possibly worried about it, but regains his faith. Declinations; David Rockefeller policy of not serving as fund-raising trustee. Summarized reports; appointment to ad hoc neighboring committee, 1953. Materials for report on Institutional Philosophies - Harvard and University of Chicago. Noted for David Rockefeller's introduction of Kimpton, 1953, and Convocation Speech, 1954. Correspondents include David Rockefeller, Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel, Thomas M. Debevoise, Edward Ryerson, Harold Swift
    - 1941-1955 (Box 115, Folder 849)
    - 1942-1949 (Box 115, Folder 850)
    - 1950-1952 (Box 115, Folder 851)
    - 1955-1961 (Box 115, Folder 852)
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - David Rockefeller - Contributions, 1941-1962 (Box 115, Folder 853)
    To alumni fund and Trustees Fund, annually, 1941-1962. To various fellowship and memorial funds; 1954 contribution to fund campaign; 1961 Pledge of $500,000 over five years.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - David Rockefeller - University of Chicago Alumni Association, 1942-1961 (Box 116, Folder 854)
    Small annual gifts. David Rockefeller became life member. Arranged luncheon for George Beadle, 1961.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - David Rockefeller - Chicago Cancer Research Foundation, 1954-1955 (Box 116, Folder 855)
    1955 declination of invitation.
  - Colleges - University of Hawaii, 1949-1961 (Box 116, Folder 856)
    Unsuccessful attempts to interest John D. Rockefeller 3rd in University. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Dana S. Creel, D. McLean.
  - Colleges - University of Hawaii - Center for Cultural and Technical Interchange, 1961-1965 (Box 116, Folder 857)
    Donald McLean attended conference on East-West relations; conference activities and follow-up. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Donald H. McLean.
  - Colleges - University of Hawaii - Center for Cultural and Technical Interchange, 1961 (Box 116, Folder 858)
  - Colleges - University of Hawaii - Center for Cultural and Technical Interchange - East-West Center Team Visit to Asia, 1960 (Box 116, Folder 859)
    Report.
  - Colleges - University of Maryland, 1959-1961 (Box 116, Folder 860)
    Laurance S. Rockefeller contributed to series of lectures on Government and Politics. John D. Rockefeller 3rd offered honorary degree; he declined. Correspondents include Laurance S. Rockefeller, Dana S. Creel, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Elmer Plischke.
    Open per BJA, July 28, 2004.
  - Colleges - University of Nebraska, 1902-1950 (Box 116, Folder 861)
    John D. Rockefeller contributed $70,000 toward building a "social and religious" center in 1904. University asked for restatement of terms of gift in 1930 and 1950; Rockefellers made no conditions re gift and didn't become involved in later analysis of use of building. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Starr J. Murphy, Willard S. Richardson, E. B. Andrews.
  - Colleges - University of Chicago - Oriental Educational Investigation - Journal, 1908-1909 (Box 116A, Folder 862)
  - Colleges - University of Pennsylvania, 1920-1960 (Box 117, Folder 863)
    Appeals for aid usually declined; some small gifts for special purposes. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Dana S. Creel, Harold Stassen.
  - Colleges - University of Pennsylvania - Department of Industrial Research, 1923-1927 (Box 117, Folder 864)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributions to division of Wharton School of Business.
  - Colleges - University of Pennsylvania - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), 1920-1926 (Box 117, Folder 865)
    Request declined.
  - Colleges - University of Pennsylvania - International Students' Work, 1923-1930 (Box 117, Folder 866)
  - Colleges - University of Pennsylvania - Museum - Exploration Fund, 1925-1929 (Box 117, Folder 867)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. a member; declination of appeals to expand funding for museum building. Excavating city of Bethshan; John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gifts, 1926-1930. Correspondents include Thomas B. Appleget, Raymond B. Fosdick, Arthur W. Packard, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., C. Harrison, Dr. G. Gordon.
  - Colleges - University of Pennsylvania - Museum - Exploration Fund, 1932-1960 (Box 117, Folder 868)
  - Colleges - University of Pennsylvania - Museum - Piedras Negras Expedition, 1932-1933 (Box 117, Folder 869)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gives $5,000 to aid expedition in Guatemala; a one-time emergency gift.
  - Colleges - University of Pennsylvania - Museum - Gift of Assyrian Bas Reliefs, 1927-1930 (Box 117, Folder 870)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. buys sculptures, houses them at Museum until 1930, when he sold them to the Metropolitan Museum.
  - Colleges - University of Pennsylvania - Museum - "Our Debt to Greece and Rome", 1925-1935 (Box 117, Folder 871)
    Set of volumes designed to be "the finest defense of the classics in the English language." They weren't, and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. refused to increase his contribution.
  - Colleges - University of Rochester, 1899-1920 (Box 118, Folder 872)
    Series of appeals. In 1920, General Education Board gave $5,000,000 to endow School of Medicine. Alan Valentine vs. Raymond B. Fosdick correspondence between John D. Rockefeller and Martin Anderson; declinations of various invitations. Correspondents include Starr J. Murphy, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Abraham Flexner, Dr. Rush Rhees, George Eastman, Alan Valentine.
  - Colleges - University of Rochester, 1920-1927 (Box 118, Folder 873)
  - Colleges - University of Rochester, 1929-1955 (Box 118, Folder 874)
  - Colleges - University of Rochester - Theological Seminary, 1925 (Box 118, Folder 875)
    Want to unite Newton and Rochester Baptist Seminaries. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. avoids involvement.
  - Colleges - University of Rochester - 1928 Pledge for Woelfkin Memorial, 1928-1931 (Box 118, Folder 876)
  - Colleges - University of Southern California, 1929-1955 (Box 118, Folder 877)
    Appeals for aid, all declined. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Thomas B. Appleget, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Colleges - University of Texas, 1941-1947 (Box 118, Folder 878)
    Appeal to Nelson A. Rockefeller to help create a center for Latin American studies at University. Never made as formal request; no action taken. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, Arthur W. Packard.
  - Colleges - University of Texas, 1958-1961 (Box 118, Folder 0878A)
  - Colleges - Vanderbilt University - School of Religion
    Request that John D. Rockefeller, Jr. assist in establishing non-denominational seminary at Vanderbilt. Willard S. Richardson very much in favor of it. General Education Board contribution. Later request in 1924; Willard S. Richardson checked with Frederick T. Gates who was strongly opposed. Reports on progress made with $25,000 for five years given by John D. Rockefeller, Jr. in 1926. Interesting commentary on religious giving by Frederick T. Gates, who did not favor John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s "modernist" stand when he took it, but once it was taken stood behind him on it. Reluctance based on political reasons. 1931 Pledge of $25,000 for five years; $500,000 conditional pledge toward endowment. 1954 Sealantic gift. Declinations of various invitations, appeals, and proposed honors. Correspondents include J. H. Kirkland, O. E. Brown, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Willard S. Richardson, Dr. Harvie Branscomb.
    - 1915-1927 (Box 119, Folder 879)
    - 1928-1932 (Box 119, Folder 880)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 119, Folder 881)
    - 1936-1953 (Box 119, Folder 882)
  - Colleges - Vassar College
    John D. Rockefeller and Frederick T. Gates trustees, 1896-1905. John D. Rockefeller contributed toward building, aid to students, books. Problems of a women's college. 1904 gift to endowment. Andrew Carnegie on extravagance in Vassar's buildings. Comparisons of Bryn Mawr and Vassar. Remodeling Rockefeller Hall; fire in 1918. Salary increases, 1922. Contributions by special projects by John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Laurance S. Rockefeller, Nelson A. Rockefeller. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Laurance S. Rockefeller, Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Frederick T. Gates, Starr J. Murphy, J. M. Taylor.
    - 1895-1912 (Box 119, Folder 883)
    - 1916-1950 (Box 119, Folder 884)
    - 1953-1961 (Box 119, Folder 885)
    - 1961 (Box 119, Folder 885A)
  - Colleges - Vassar College - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Correspondence, 1933-1959 (Box 119, Folder 886)
    Gifts to Vassar; John D. Rockefeller 3rd's friendship with administration. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Sarah G. Blandling.
  - Colleges - Vassar College - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 119, Folder 886A)
  - Colleges - Vassar College - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Gift, December 1956, 1956-1957 (Box 119, Folder 887)
    Toward rebuilding main building.
  - Colleges - Vassar College - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Gift, December 1956, 1956-1957 (Box 119, Folder 887A)
  - Colleges - Vassar College - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Gift, December 1955, 1955-1956 (Box 119, Folder 888)
    To establish a chair in music.
  - Colleges - Vassar College - Laurance S. Rockefeller and Mary F. Rockefeller, 1935-1961 (Box 119, Folder 889)
  - Colleges - University of Virginia, 1904-1911 (Box 120, Folder 890)
    Frederick T. Gates and Starr J. Murphy on early operations of General Education Board. John D. Rockefeller gift of $100,000. Interest in University of office staff. Declinations. Correspondents include Frederick T. Gates, Starr J. Murphy, John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Dana S. Creel, O. Villard.
  - Colleges - University of Virginia, 1921-1961 (Box 120, Folder 891)
  - Colleges - University of Virginia, 1956 (Box 120, Folder 0891A)
  - Colleges - Washington University, St. Louis, Missouri, 1946-1956 (Box 120, Folder 892)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. declines to underwrite scholarships for Chinese students. Conference on "Science and Human Responsibility" - John D. Rockefeller 3rd invited; declines. Edgar B. Young invites President Compton to address New Jersey organization, The Athenaeum. Correspondents include Arthur Compton, Laurance S. Rockefeller, Edgar B. Young.
  - Colleges - Wellesley College, 1899-1905 (Box 120, Folder 893)
    Poor financial condition, 1899-1900; 1900 controversy over accepting "tainted money" as faculty members urged against accepting Rockefeller gift. Professor Jenks of Cornell arbitrated, and Wellesley took the money. Grant for heating plant. Construction of heating system very poor; reconstruction necessary. John D. Rockefeller gave further assistance. Contributions ended with creation of General Education Board. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contribution to rebuild Stone Hall after fire. Contributions by Nelson A. Rockefeller and Laurance S. Rockefeller. Correspondents include Caroline Hoyard, John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Nelson A. Rockefeller, Laurance S. Rockefeller, Frederick T. Gates.
  - Colleges - Wellesley College, 1907-1961 (Box 120, Folder 894)
  - Colleges - Wellesley College, 1959-1961 (Box 120, Folder 894A)
  - Colleges - Wellesley College - Power Plant, 1900-1907 (Box 120, Folder 895)
    Conditional gift to rebuild power plant.
  - Colleges - Wells College, Aurora, New York, 1931-1940 (Box 120, Folder 896)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. made $14,000 gift toward building, 1931, anonymously. Declined later requests. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Raymond B. Fosdick, Arthur W. Packard.
  - Colleges - Western College for Women, Oxford, Ohio, 1922-1960 (Box 120, Folder 897)
    Training women for religious service. General Education Board grants. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. declines appeal for building funds and endowment for Bible Department. David Rockefeller declines appeal and invitation to deliver 1959 Commencement Address. President Young asks David Rockefeller to help provide scholarship for Tom Mboya's 1954 fianc - question of political dangers no matter how David Rockefeller responds. David Rockefeller refers case to African-American Institute. Correspondents include W. W. Boyd, Willard S. Richardson, Herrick B. Young, David Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Colleges - Western College for Women, Oxford, Ohio, 1955-1960 (Box 120, Folder 0897A)
  - Colleges - Western Reserve University, Cleveland, Ohio - Medical School and Other Correspondence, 1905-1912 (Box 121, Folder 898)
    John D. Rockefeller's contribution; John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s interest in it. 1905 Report on school by Starr J. Murphy; General Education Board investigation. Medical School got $250,000. Later appeals all declined. Correspondents include Starr J. Murphy, Frederick T. Gates, John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Colleges - Western Reserve University, Cleveland, Ohio - Medical School and Other Correspondence, 1913-1952 (Box 121, Folder 899)
  - Colleges - Yale University
    John D. Rockefeller gave $1,000,000 toward endowment, 1905. General Education Board gave $300,000. Long, detailed report on Yale by Starr J. Murphy. Requests for small gifts declined. Reports on activities; requests for interviews. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gift to James Rowland Angell Memorial Fund. Winthrop Rockefeller contributions. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Starr J. Murphy, Frederick T. Gates, A. S. Phelps, Winthrop Rockefeller.
    - 1902-1905 (Box 121, Folder 900)
    - Report, 1903 (Box 121, Folder 901)
    - 1907-1947 (Box 121, Folder 902)
    - 1948-1950 (Box 121, Folder 903)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 121, Folder 0903A)
    - 1950-1961 (Box 121, Folder 904)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 121, Folder 0904A)
  - Colleges - Yale University - Yale in China Association, 1941-1961 (Box 121, Folder 905)
    Winthrop Rockefeller contribution.
  - Colleges - Yale University - Excavation Fund, 1925-1927 (Box 121, Folder 906)
    Appeal for aid declined.
  - Colleges - Yale University - Alcohol Research and Service Program, 1944-1952 (Box 121, Folder 907)
  - Colleges - Yale University - Interseminary Commission for Training for the Rural Ministry, 1929-1933 (Box 121, Folder 908)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave $28,000 annually for three years to assist in training of ministers for rural areas. Program carried on at several New England Theological Seminaries; renewal of gift, at lower rate, for three additional years. Later gift made by Davison Fund. Reports on work completed. Correspondents include Willard S. Richardson, Arthur W. Packard, Thomas B. Appleget.
  - Colleges - Yale University - Interseminary Commission for Training for the Rural Ministry, 1934-1940 (Box 121, Folder 909)
  - Colleges - Yale University - Interseminary Commission for Training for the Rural Ministry - June 20, 1929 Pledge Payments, 1929-1932 (Box 121, Folder 910)
  - Colleges - Yale University - Interseminary Commission for Training for the Rural Ministry - April 25, 1932 Pledge and Payments, 1932-1933 (Box 121, Folder 911)
  - Colleges - Yale University - Divinity School, 1925-1929 (Box 122, Folder 912)
    1925 appeal; Frederick T. Gates says that Yale should take the lead. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gives up to $1,000,000 conditionally; time extensions. 1930 resolution of gratitude by John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Dr. Liston Pope's description of American theological education, 1952. Sealantic Fund gift, $1,500,000 in 1955. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. declines to have new quad named after him. Correspondents include Willard S. Richardson, Frederick T. Gates, James Angell, C. R. Brown, Liston Pope, Dana S. Creel.
  - Colleges - Yale University - Divinity School, 1930-1957 (Box 122, Folder 913)
  - Colleges - Yale University - Divinity School - February 21, 1927 Pledge and Extensions, 1927-1939 (Box 122, Folder 914)
  - Colleges - Yeshiva University, 1951-1959 (Box 122, Folder 915)